[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "name": "Math",
    "list": [
      {
        "question": "2 * 3 = ?",
        "answer": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "3 * 3 = ?",
        "answer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "4 * 3 = ?",
        "answer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "5 * 3 = ?",
        "answer": "15"
      },
      {
        "question": "6 * 3 = ?",
        "answer": "18"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Italian",
    "list": [
      {
        "question": "Rossi",
        "answer": "Красный"
      },
      {
        "question": "Anche",
        "answer": "также"
      },
      {
        "question": "Scuola",
        "answer": "школа"
      },
      {
        "question": "Naso",
        "answer": "нос"
      },
      {
        "question": "Divano",
        "answer": "диван"
      }
    ]
  }
]
